<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Russian Trolls</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Russian Trolls</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump</title>
      <link>/2018/12/09/trump/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/09/trump/</guid>
      <description>knitr::include_graphics(&amp;quot;/post/trump.png&amp;quot;) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Trump Phrases</title>
      <link>/2018/12/05/daily-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/05/daily-tweets/</guid>
      <description>Here I decided to take a look at some of Trump’s most popular catchphrases as told by Russian trolls associated with the IRA. If you want to learn more about the data here, please check out the About Page and if you want to learn more about how I’m using the data, check out a previous post on this data set. Meanwhile, I’m here to tell you some of the stories the data helps to show!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Russian Tweets in the 2016 Presidential Election</title>
      <link>/2018/12/03/daily-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/12/03/daily-tweets/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the 2016 US Presidential Election, Tweets were published by trolls associated with the Internet Research Agency (IRA) - a Russian entity. The IRA is believed to have been tasked with interfering in the 2016 US Presidential Election with their primary goal being to disseminate news and opinions in a way that motivated the spread of disinformation in a critical time in US politics.
In 2016, the two primary candidates up for the US Presidency were Donald J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Enxhi Buxheli and I am currently a junior at Harvard College concentrating in Physics. I am fascinated by data and all the stories that you can tell using with it. The purpose of this specific website is to tell the story of the Russian Trolls in the 2016 US Presidential Election. The data used to form these stories came from a join FiveThirtyEight and Clemson University dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>